

Mykyta Reva



+48575703245



MYKYTAREVA@GMAIL.COM

CUSTOMER SERVICE REPRESENTATIVE

CAREER OBJECTIVE

I am experienced customer service representative with strong knowledge of English and with good understanding basic customers needs. I am responsible and pro-active person, I am ready for new opportunities and for getting new skills in this area.

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- Official responses through emails
- Full-cycle assistance chats/calls
- Time managment
- Excel/Microsoft Word

EDUCATION

Odesa National Maritime University Navigator (09.2019 - 06.2023)

Hillel IT School Python Backend Developer (07.2022 -12.2023)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Call Center Operator Ryanair Airlines

- providing assistance through live channels such as Calls and Live Chat with native speakers
- providing assistance through e- mails (April 2022 - now)

Seaspan Corporation Seaman in mixed crew

I worked as a deck cadet in a mixed crew. (September 2021 - April 2022)